

Taytay, Rizal PHILIPPINES 1920

felicio.sharon@gmail.com #63 9173693010 skype ID: sharon.felicio22

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in *Mathematics* major in Computer Science Far Eastern University 1999-2003

EXPERTISE

CUSTOMER CARE
SOCIAL MEDIA
MS OFFICE
PHOTOSHOP
GRAPHICS
WEB PAGE DESIGN
BASIC CODING - (HTML / CSS)
BASIC PROGRAMMING (JQUERY/ JAVASCRIPT)
BASIC ACCOUNTING
DATA ENTRY
ADMIN. SUPPORT

SHARON FELICIO

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT | SOCIAL MEDIA | DATA MANAGER | WEB DESIGNER | GHAPHIC ARTIST

ABOUT ME

Over <u>ten years</u> of working experience in general office setting, providing clerical, customer service and supervisory in variety of settings including Banks, BPO and Hotels. Defined as an adaptable, self-motivated, confident and very realiable individual. I'm efficient and responsible worker, making me a valuable asset to any team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

present- 2017	FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER/ GRAPHIICS Design Webpages - HTML/CSS/JQuery/Javascript Wordpress Development/Shopify
present- 2013	CAKE ARTIST BAKER ENTREPRENEUR Kalel's Sweet Tooth (Homebased Business) - PH Own and manage small online cake shop. Bake, decorate and sell cakes online. https://www.facebook.com/kalelssweettooth
2010 - 2012	HOUSEKEEPING SUPERVISOR/ ATTENDANT Sawridge Inn and Confernce Centre - CANADA Train and supervise housekeeping personnel. Submit daily report to the General Manager. Prepare daily task to housekeeping team.
2008 - 2010	FOOD COUNTER ATTENDANT/ CASHIER Marmot Basin Ski Resort (winter season)- CANADA FRONT DESK AGENT Pine Bungalows (summer season) - CANADA
2006 - 2008	RECEPTIONIST ADMINISTRATIVE STAFF Concentrix Technologist Inc PH
2005 - 2006	CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE Teleperformance - PH HTMT Source 1 Asia - PH
2003 - 2005	BANK TELLER ACCOUNTING CLERK Banco De Oro Unibank - PH RCBC Savings Bank - PH